Github

LinkedIn

Ahmedabad, Gujarat 7861824698 yash1971saini@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

My goal is to be associated with a company where I can utilise my skills and gain further experience while enhancing the company's productivity and reputation, one which will make best use of my existing skills and experience and also further my development along with the growth of the organisation.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering

Government Engineering College, Gandhinagar 2019 - 2023

Higher Secondary

The Mahatma Gandhi School, Ahmedabad 2018 - 2019

Secondary

The Rosery School, Ahmedabad 2017 - 2018

EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL

Creart Solutions OPC PVT. LTD. (Internship)

JUNE 2022 - JULY 2022

Worked on a Web Email sending application by which we can directly send the mail to the recipient from the application.

CrawlMagic Solutions (Internship)

February 2023 - May 2023

Trained in Django as well in Django Rest Framework.

NON-TECHNICAL

NBLIK INDIA PVT. LTD.

SEP 2021 - FEB 2022

Responsible for generating lead for the growth of the company

PROMOTED | OPERATIONS

Responsible for maintaining employee experience and help building healthy environment Management of interns at various levels.

PROMOTED | COMMUNITY MANAGER

Responsible for managing the community in the NBLIK App Responsible for inspecting the effectiveness of the events on an app.

PROJECTS

- Ride Hailing Web Application (Similar to Uber that contains Authentication and Authorization System)
- **GUI** (Using Python Library TKINTER)
- HomeAutomation using LAN

SKILLS

• TECHNICAL

Python

HTML

Java

CSS

MySQL

C++

JavaScript

NON-TECHNICAL

Communication Skills Management Adaptability Problem Solving

LANGUAGE

Hindi (Native) English (Fluent) Gujarati(Fluent)

Declaration

I, Yash Saini, hereby declare that the information contained herein is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.